...that says "allergic to penicillin."
(Sheldon:)Maybe they have
a dressier version of that.
(Assistant:)How are we doing this afternoon?
Looking for anything special?
(Assistant:)Perhaps a ring for the lady?
(Penny:)Trust me, we are not a couple.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me. I don't see why
you get to snort derisively...
(Sheldon:)...and point that out.
You'd be lucky to land a fellow like me.
(Penny:)Fine. Go ahead.
(Penny:)Trust me, we are not a couple.
(Assistant:)My apologies.
How can I help you today?
He's in trouble with his girIfriend,
needs a present.
Great. Trouble with girIfriends is what's
putting my daughter through U.S.C.
(Sheldon:)Ooh!
- Are those real diamonds?
- Yes.
Channel-set baguettes,
20 points total weight.
(Sheldon:)Remarkable. Diamonds.
Crystallized carbon.
(Sheldon:)Every day, people go to the grocery
store and come home with sacks...
(Sheldon:)...full of carbon in the form
of charcoal briquettes...
...they toss in their barbecues
and set on fire.
(Sheldon:)But just because you've got some
carbon with the atoms stacked neatly...